['Company', 'Total Car-Miles'],
['Bittner, Hunsicker & Co. (Allentown, PA, 1 car)', 192.68],
['Fate-Root-Heath Co. (Plymouth Locomotive Works) (Plymouth, OH, 1 car)', 308.48],
['Comly-Flanigan & Co. (Philadelphia, PA, 1 car)', 217.33],
['Lippincott & Co. (Altoona, PA, 1 car)', 12.76],
['Reeves, Parvin & Co. (Philadelphia, PA, 1 car)', 241.36],
['Dean Coal Co. Fruhlinger Colliery No. 1 (Dean, PA, 2 cars)', 39.68],
['Dean Coal Co. Unknown (Coalport, PA, 1 car)', 31.29],
['Western Wheeled Scraper Co. (Aurora, IL, 1 car)', 700.44],
['Penna. Coal & Coke Co. Penna. Coll. No. 10 (Ehrenfeld, PA, 1 car)', 36.91],
['Butler Bros. Co. (Jersey City, NJ, 3 cars)', 876.77],
['Atlas Powder Co. (Horrell, PA, 1 car)', 4.19],
['Daniel Miller Co. (Baltimore, MD, 2 cars)', 275.87],
['Gorman-Rupp Co. (Mansfield, OH, 2 cars)', 594.47],
['Penn General Supply Co. (Pittsburgh, PA, 2 cars)', 242.86],
['Thew Shovel Co./Universal Crane Co. (Lorain, OH, 5 cars)', 1397.71],
['American Fork & Hoe Co. Skelton Shovel Works (Dunkirk, NY, 1 car)', 161.63],
['Frick-Reid Supply Corp. (Pittsburgh, PA, 2 cars)', 242.67],
['M.B.& A.H. Christy (Trenton, NJ, 1 car)', 241.36],
['Burton-Dixie Corp. (Brooklyn, NY, 1 car)', 295.93],
['Mishawaka Rubber & Woolen Mfg. Co. (Mishawaka, IN, 1 car)', 555.99],
['Brown Shoe Co. (St. Louis, MO, 2 cars)', 1672.50],
['A. M. Byers Co. (Economy, PA (Ambridge), 1 car)', 137.67],
['Bethlehem Steel Co. Lackawanna Plant (Lackawanna, NY, 2 cars)', 342.13],
['Bethlehem Steel Co. Sparrows Point Plant (Sparrows Point, MD, 4 cars)', 587.34],
['Bowers Pottery Co. (Mannington, WV, 2 cars)', 313.20],
['Canadian Porcelain Co. (Hamilton, Ontario , 1 car)', 227.71],
['Carnegie-Illinois Steel Co. Mingo Works (Carnegie Steel) (Mingo Junction, OH , 5 cars)', 815.59],
['Carnegie-Illinois Steel Co. Edgar Thompson Works (Carnegie Steel) (Bessemer, PA , 2 cars)', 222.42],
['Carnegie-Illinois Steel Co. South Works (Illinois Steel) (South Chicago, IL, 1 car)', 649.10],
['General Refractories Co. Sproul (Sproul, PA , 3 cars)', 52.41],
['General Refractories Co. Joliet (Joliet, IL , 2 cars)', 1370.75],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. East Chicago (East Chicago, IL , 1 car)', 642.73],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. Ensley (Ensley, AL , 1 car)', 767.61],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. No. 8 Works (Woodland, PA (Mineral Spring), 10 cars)', 413.09],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. Mount Union (Mount Union, PA, 8 cars)', 199.87],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. Retort Works (Retort, PA, 19 cars)', 539.01],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. Lower Works (Woodland, PA, 4 cars)', 166.71],
['Harbison-Walker Refractory Co. Barrett Works (Woodland, PA (Barrett), 14 cars)', 594.71],
['Lapp Insulator Co. (Le Roy, NY, 1 car)', 178.13],
['Locke Insulator Co. (Baltimore, MD, 7 cars)', 967.25],
['McFeely Brick Co. (Latrobe, PA, 2 cars)', 155.58],
['National Tube Co. Lorain Works (Lorain, OH, 3 cars)', 832.02],
['North American Refractory Co. (Mount Union, PA, 7 cars)', 181.93],
['Smith & Stone, Ltd. (Georgetown, Ontario, 2 cars)', 506.40],
['Taylor, Smith & Taylor (Chester, WV, 2 cars)', 320.94],
['United Clay Mines Corp. (Trenton, NJ, 1 car)', 240.76],
['Victor Insulators, Inc. (Victor, NY, 1 car)', 186.98],
['Wheeling Steel Corp. Benwood Works (Benwood, WV, 1 car)', 174.30],
['Youngstown Sheet & Tube Co. Campbell Works Converting Mills (Youngstown, OH, 3 cars)', 507.68]